We don't have some of those sounds in my language. This is undoubtedly true, but
you can see that you only need to pick up a limited number of new sounds, ah, ah,
ah, uh, uh. Given what you've already accomplished in life, this is not a big
deal. A Chinese speaker was once bemoaning how hard it was for him to say the R. When
asked if he went to college, he said, of course, I have a PhD in physics from
Caltech. After a beat, he realized that, compared to that, the R is not hard. Other
characters. If you use one of these character sets, compare it with English.
Let me give a quick explanation of why we're using these sounds. When you come in
through your own language, you're coming from a place of total and absolute
confidence. You know that sound, so we're taking something you know and doing a
lateral transference to a set of letters in English. If on the other hand you start
from scratch, you'll be wondering if you're doing it right and this will drain
your confidence and your energy. Now that you've worked hard and successfully
imitated the sounds, you're going to go on to the next step, which is regular
spelling.